Name: 李梓琦 LI ZIQI Mobile Number: +86 1327 5922 779 E-Mail: liziqi\_@hotmail.com

## **Profile**

Through the study overseas and the multi-nation working experience from the past 13 years, I trained myself to be a highly self-motivated, task-oriented, open-minded and someone who is willing to spend extra to learn new skill-sets to meet the demands of my job.

Based on the most recent working experience, which has the different cultural background, I have learned more professional workspaces rules and better manage the workplace relationship for different cultural background, most importantly, I have a better understanding about my abilities and passions.

I am looking for a full-time job as a software developer, where I hope to be an asset to the company with my skills and experience.

Education Information				
07.2014 - 12.2017	Nanyang Technological University	Computer Engineering	Degree	
03.2011 - 04.2014	Singapore Polytechnic	Info-Communication & Design	Diploma	
08.2007 - 12.2010	Montfort Secondary School		GCE O Level	
Work Experience				

01.2018 - Now M

Motic China Group Co., Ltd

Software Developer

Worked as a software developer in the Development Department, and mainly handle the following tasks:

- > Using Android Studio to maintain the Android application:
  - To develop new features.
  - To fix bugs.
  - To brief the updates to the Production Line, and train the staff.
- ➤ Use Shell Scripting to patch the software on the Linux platform remotely.
- Self-learning Matlab, and take in charge of a new project with an American company, and handle the following tasks:
  - Code Conversion, which is: Converting Matlab Code to C++ Code.
  - Code Maintenance (Git), such as source code updates, the documentation maintenance.
  - Scrum Meeting, such as: to communicate with the other side to resolve the bugs, report the progress.

Worked as a software developer in the IBM Software Department – Deployment Automation Team, and mainly using Shell Scripting to handle the following tasks:

- Self-learning Jenkins then adopted a new authentication method on IBM Jenkins Server, e.g. LDAP (Lightweight Directory Access Protocol).
- ➤ Self-learning Docker, then work with the docker containers e.g. deploy the Docker containers.
- > Self-learning IBM WAS (WebSphere Application Server) and patching the server.
- ➤ Self-learning IBM BPM (Business Process Manager) and patching the server.
- > Self-learning IBM UCD (Urban Code Deployment) and use it as a tool for the deployment automation.
- ➤ Self-learning the software version control GitHub.

05.2017 - 07.2017

Motic China Group Co. Ltd.

Intern

Worked as a software developer in the Software Development Department. Mainly doing the following tasks:

- ➤ Migrate a Visual Studio 2008 based program to Visual Studio 2013 based program.
- ➤ Integrate with Motic protection mechanism, e.g. hardware dongle and software license.
- Integrate with Motic hardware, e.g. the Motic camera series.
- ➤ Get familiar with the migration of the Matlab solution to C++ language based.

08.2015 - 11.2015

Project Manager

Gathered a team of five to provide services to a company. E.g. Android, IOS and web page development for their online ticket ordering system for the bus services.

11.2014-06.2015

S&Z Pte Ltd.

Entrepreneur

Join a start-up software company which is launched by a friend from NTU. I played a part as a helper in recruitment and project planning.

Awards	
2012	Singapore Polytechnic - Merit Award - Singapore Technologies Telemedia Prize
2012	Singapore Polytechnic - Director's Honour Roll
2013	Singapore Polytechnic - Merit Award - Hutcabb Prize
2013	Singapore Polytechnic - Director's Honour Roll
2014	Singapore Polytechnic - Merit Award - Singapore Technologies Telemedia Prize
2014	Singapore Polytechnic - Diploma With Merit
2018	Nanyang Technological University – Degree with Honours (Merit)

## Skills & Abilities

Language Proficiency English and Chinese (Written & Spoken)

Programming Background Java, C, C++, C#, Python and Visual Basic.